<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-10T06:24:41-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Alternative Beach-Bali</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/05/alternative-beach-bali.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alternative Beach-Bali" /><published>2019-04-05T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-04-05T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/05/alternative-beach-bali</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/05/alternative-beach-bali.html">&lt;p&gt;Have you been to Bali yet? If not I highly suggest you go. The cafes and restaurants are amazing and you can’t go wrong. I am always on the hunt for a new cafe, restaurant, or chill out place when I travel. Luckily in Bali, I found Alternative Beach! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/alternative-beach-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We first came here with the group from Institute of Code (more on that later) and I was blown away by all the suitable “instagram worthy” shots available. I swear, they designed this place in mind specifically for all you fabulous Instagrammers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, the place is a hostel and a hotel all in one! Perfect for you budget travellers who love the hostel life, and crafted for the romantic lovers who want a private pool front villa. Creator thought of everything to appeal to the mass audiences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who doesn’t love a pool bar? I have no idea! Can’t think of a single person who’s had to complain and get out of the water to get their drink. Just swim on up order a cocktail, and sip it on one of the many floats they have available in the pool. Or chill out on the beachside walk in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/alternative-beach-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to work on your Bali Bod? (I think that should be new hashtag on instagram) They have you covered. Wanderlust Fitness Studio. Yes That is the name of the gym on the premises. Sadly I was enjoying the outdoors to much to go inside, but I saw it through a window. Looked Fabulous. Time to get fit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fact is short is sweet, when in Canggu head over to Alternative Beach for an evening of fun, drinks, laughter, and sweet content for your instagram that will last you weeks! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/alternative-beach-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Travel" /><summary type="html">Have you been to Bali yet? If not I highly suggest you go. The cafes and restaurants are amazing and you can’t go wrong. I am always on the hunt for a new cafe, restaurant, or chill out place when I travel. Luckily in Bali, I found Alternative Beach! </summary></entry></feed>