<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-15T19:34:43-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><subtitle>Brylee Williamson blog dedicated to helping you live your dream life!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Infamous Red Dress- Rove Byron Bay</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/26/infamous-red-dress-rove-byron-bay.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Infamous Red Dress- Rove Byron Bay" /><published>2019-05-26T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/26/infamous-red-dress--rove-byron-bay</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/26/infamous-red-dress-rove-byron-bay.html">&lt;p&gt;The infamous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rovedesigns.com/products/sevilla-dress&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Red Dress&lt;/a&gt;! The most beautiful dress I’ve seen in photos. Seriously, this dress can be used in any situation. Thankfully, Tina with Institute of Code allowed us to borrow it to use. I hope Rove Byron Bay will let me get my own to continue to shoot with! Take a look! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/red-dress-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;1080&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/red-dress-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;1080&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/red-dress-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;1080&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/red-dress-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;1080&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/red-dress-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;720&quot; height=&quot;1080&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Modeling" /><summary type="html">The infamous Red Dress! The most beautiful dress I’ve seen in photos. Seriously, this dress can be used in any situation. Thankfully, Tina with Institute of Code allowed us to borrow it to use. I hope Rove Byron Bay will let me get my own to continue to shoot with! Take a look! </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nusa Penida- Courtesy of Nusa Penida Travels</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/05/22/nusa-penida-courtesy-of-nusa-penida-travels.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nusa Penida- Courtesy of Nusa Penida Travels" /><published>2019-05-22T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-22T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/05/22/nusa-penida--courtesy-of-nusa-penida-travels</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/05/22/nusa-penida-courtesy-of-nusa-penida-travels.html">&lt;p&gt;NUSA PENIDA!!! I had been dreaming of this place since I first saw it posted on Instagram. I dreamed of seeing the T-Rex beach as well as the Tree-Houses. So, when I decided I was going to do the Coding and Social Media Bootcamp with Institute of Code, I had to make time to go to Nusa Penida!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read Nusa Penida can be very tricky and difficult to navigate on your own so I decided to do a tour with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nusapenidatravels.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nusa Penida Travels.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously this made the trip 1000x easier than I think it could have. It was so simple, the tour group was friendly, and I couldn’t have asked for a better company to take my friends and I through &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nusapenidatravels.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nusa Penida&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at where they took us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day 1: North and East Nusa Penida&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our day started with a pickup from our hotel at 6 am. Yeah super early but we were in Canguu so it was worth it. We had to get to the Sanur Harbor by 8 am and the company completely arranged our boat tickets for us! The boat ride was a bit choppy that day but so fun! All 3 of us were tired but we were ready for the day ahead!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started at the Rumah Pohon treehouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Treehouses are incredible! There is actually a way to stay at them but be warned, Bali is HOT! They are on the side of the island with sunrise, so if you stay overnight, you will get the sunrise of a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-38.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While you’re already at the treehouses you get a view of Diamond Beach as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then went to Atuh Beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-43.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was by far the highlight of the trip! The beach is so quiet, mostly locals with their shops, a few tourists. But the sand was white, and the water was so warm. We spent our day taking photos, having a cocktail and eating some local great food!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-42.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think total we saw maybe 10 other tourists! I think many people skip this spot to for Diamond Beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diamond Beach&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-36.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diamond beach is probably the second most popular photo you see on Instagram these days. The beach is flawless. You are able to climb the stairs down to the bottom, but it looked like a journey. I was so tired by this point; I couldn’t do it. I also found out, after I left there is a swing in the area! Must do for the next trip!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** please take note, this beach is not good for swimming due to strong currents and the coral in the area **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was the end of day 1. We were so exhausted, already sunburned but having a blast!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we booked with Nusa Penida Travels, they booked our hotel for us too. It was beautiful! There was a pool, a huge bathroom, and AC!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tour company owner even came to meet us, take us to dinner and chat. We went to this beautiful little café by the beach, and had an amazing view of Mt. Agung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nusapenidatravels.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nusa Penida travels&lt;/a&gt; not only books you a tour but, treats you like family!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day 2: West Nusa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelingking View Point&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-56.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FINALLY! The place I was waiting for. We had to go see the famous T-Rex beach. We wanted to beat the crowds so we were up at 6:15 to get to the spot. Best Decision ever. When we got there, only 2 other people were in sight! It was amazing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We beat all the crowds because as soon as we left, the crowds came piling in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a way to make it to the bottom, but you need to have comfortable shoes, and lots of time and water. We ran into some people who made the trek to the bottom, they were exhausted! If you do this, I suggest going right at sunrise or a bit before to avoid the heat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then onto Angels billabong&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me start of by saying, I think this is the part where I thought we were going to die.  I could see us so close to the edge of the road I was so scared. The roads aren’t big enough for 2 cars but somehow, they make it work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we arrived, I was so thankful we had the best tour guide because he brought his drone! We managed to get some amazing drone shots! He even made sure we were safe getting into the water and took some awesome outtakes for us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-59.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make your way to Broken Beach&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Broken beach is another stunning viewpoint. It was tranquil and peaceful to sit and just watch the water move. This would be palace for a picnic or just a place to sit with yourself and your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snorkeling with manta rays!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take note, this is all through the tour company which I highly suggest because, they go above and beyond to make sure you see the rays. They provided, water, towels and snacks for us on the boat!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the highlight everyone was waiting for! All we wanted was to see manta rays! Now everyone goes to Manta Point, but by the time we got there, it was crowded and overstuffed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We managed to see a few through the cloudy water but they were so low we couldn’t get a great view. We left Manta point disappointed, but….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then while on our way back, the boat drivers found a small group of mana rays and we got to spend an entire 30 minutes with them! They were so close you could touch them! * but don’t because it is illegal* Seriously the greatest gift seeing these big beautiful creatures. Some people aren’t lucky enough to find them, but we were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is that! Our trip with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nusapenidatravels.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nusa Penida travels&lt;/a&gt; was once in a lifetime. If you plan to go to Nusa Penida, you have to make this company a priority. The roads of Nusa are so bad that if you rented a bike, you are likely to hurt yourself without experience in riding a motorbike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part of this tour company, is they don’t come from the main island and create a tour company, they are locals who put in work and that you like family while you are with them. It is their way of making a living, by providing quality service at a great price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/nusa-penida-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nusa-penida-tours&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t praise them enough for the care and quality they provided for us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Travel" /><summary type="html">NUSA PENIDA!!! I had been dreaming of this place since I first saw it posted on Instagram. I dreamed of seeing the T-Rex beach as well as the Tree-Houses. So, when I decided I was going to do the Coding and Social Media Bootcamp with Institute of Code, I had to make time to go to Nusa Penida!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quick Pitch Tip</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/social%20media/2019/05/22/quick-pitch-tip.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quick Pitch Tip" /><published>2019-05-22T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-22T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/social%20media/2019/05/22/quick-pitch-tip</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/social%20media/2019/05/22/quick-pitch-tip.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey guys! I had to share this! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was struggling with my pitches for a bit! I kept emailing a cold pitch and trying to get them to work with me right away. It became 50/50 that someone would respond because lets face it, brands are overwhelmed. Well I found this cute little trick in some groups that I really think could be helpful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tested it yesterday! I cold pitched 2 hotels and Death Valley, THEY RESPONDED!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ready for it…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think you are…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/brand-2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Pitching&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it. And I got a response from both. Try it out! Let me know how it goes! &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Social Media" /><summary type="html">Hey guys! I had to share this! </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Magic Moon Love child</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/21/magic-moon-love-child.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Magic Moon Love child" /><published>2019-05-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/21/magic-moon-love-child</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/21/magic-moon-love-child.html">&lt;p&gt;Vintage! I’m a total vintage girl. Seriously, flare jeans, weird tops, denim jackets. I see it, I want it. Sadly I ain’t got the budget for it! My friend Natalie owns a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.depop.com/magicmoonlovechild/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;depop &lt;/a&gt;shop where she shops for vintage clothes and sells them. I don’t know about you but the joy of trying to find  vintage clothing is epic. Check out my girls &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/magicmoonlovechild/ &quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and her shop for more looks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/magic-moon04.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wanted something urban to show both a sweet side and and an edgy side. Nothing better than a downtown area of Ventura! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/isaiahxaiah/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Isaiah&lt;/a&gt; knows the best places to shoot at! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also were lucky to have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/katelynn_jean_artistry/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Katelynn &lt;/a&gt;she is a miracle worker with this face!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/magic-moon08.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you like the looks we created together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Natalie’s whole goal is to bring outfits together to show a persons personality. She is a stylist and can read people from the moment she meets them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/magic-moon09.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/magic-moon02.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/magic-moon11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Modeling" /><summary type="html">Vintage! I’m a total vintage girl. Seriously, flare jeans, weird tops, denim jackets. I see it, I want it. Sadly I ain’t got the budget for it! My friend Natalie owns a depop shop where she shops for vintage clothes and sells them. I don’t know about you but the joy of trying to find  vintage clothing is epic. Check out my girls Instagram and her shop for more looks!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stop the Follow-Unfollow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/social%20media/2019/05/02/stop-the-follow-unfollow.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stop the Follow-Unfollow" /><published>2019-05-02T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-02T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/social%20media/2019/05/02/stop-the-follow-unfollow</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/social%20media/2019/05/02/stop-the-follow-unfollow.html">&lt;p&gt;Instagram Instagram Instagram I have a love/hate relationship with Instagram. Most day’s I hate it because of its always a competition. I often feel bad about myself if a photo doesn’t do good or if my likes suck. It’s also a numbers game. If you don’t have the followers you aren’t worthwhile. We have become so reliant on our self worth being based on Instagram. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this isn’t about that, well in a way it is. Followers do count on Instagram and since it has become so saturated it is harder and harder to grow. But I am asking you to stop the follow/unfollow game! It hurts you! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accounts that do follow/unfollow are deemed unhealthy by Instagram when you look at your analytics. It actually hurts you when it helps you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, your followers can see you are following and unfollowing thousands of people. No one wants to see that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me! I’ve tested it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there is a method that works with follow/unfollow but it is a bit different. I only suggest it with someone you trust. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/follow-unfollow-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My secret is creating a viral account! Yes, that is it. Create a Viral Account in your niche. Use that to leverage people to follow your own account. That’s how I grow at least 20-50 new follower a day. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you might be thinking  “ I don’t have time to grow a viral account!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry darlin I got you. I actually do this for a lower price than so many growth agencies out there. I already am growing a viral travel account as well as a second “alternate Brylee account” The Brylee account is almost at 1000 followers in less than a month and the viral Travel account is at 300 in a month. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mind you some are harder to grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There isn’t just posting viral content you have to partner with hashtags that will help you grow or no one will see it. It’s a tricky process but worth it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this process hit me up and I can help you. I promise its cheaper than those growth services that charge you to follow/unfollow on your own account. Also, I don’t need your password! &lt;br /&gt;Also better than buying likes or followers those are even worse, I’ll share more on those later. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/follow-unfollow-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Social Media" /><summary type="html">Instagram Instagram Instagram I have a love/hate relationship with Instagram. Most day’s I hate it because of its always a competition. I often feel bad about myself if a photo doesn’t do good or if my likes suck. It’s also a numbers game. If you don’t have the followers you aren’t worthwhile. We have become so reliant on our self worth being based on Instagram. </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chasing Cherry Blossoms- Okinawa</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/05/02/chasing-cherry-blossoms-okinawa.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chasing Cherry Blossoms- Okinawa" /><published>2019-05-02T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-02T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/05/02/chasing-cherry-blossoms--okinawa</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/05/02/chasing-cherry-blossoms-okinawa.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s springtime! What does that mean? CHERRY BLOSSOM SEASON! Cherry Blossoms are the staple of living in Japan. It’s the highlight of being there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also Japan’s busiest time of year. You cant even find hotels and flights jump up in prices. I swear Japan also increases prices on everything in their restaurants. They must have a special Cherry Blossom Season menu. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/cherry-blossom-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Anyways there are some beautiful Places to see the cherry blossoms. Especially in Okinawa. Many people flock to mainland and Kyoto but Okinawa has its few small hidden gems. The best time to go is late January to early February but this can change so keep an eye out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mount Yaedake&lt;/strong&gt;- The drive up here is a long one but in the end, it’s worth it. The long winding roads of Cherry Blossoms are a site to see. Many people pull over and take photos so be aware. There are designated parking areas. So please don’t be that person who just pulls over wherever they please. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nakijin Castle Ruins&lt;/strong&gt;- I was dumb and didn’t make it to this one but this is a great one I’ve read. This is also a UNESCO World Heritage site so you can kill 2 birds with one stone. From what I have read, at night the paths lined with small glass lanterns. Guess what?! Actually, they are used for the nighttime illumination. The scene you see at night sounds like a fairy tale!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nago Central Park&lt;/strong&gt;- Nago is the opposite end of Mout Yaedake so you cant make both in one day. This is the most recommended place in Okinawa. The festival time is great to go with all the local food vendors. I suggest the Yakisoba of course! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/cherry-blossom-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, these are just 3 places to see Cherry Blossoms but Oki has so many! If you just drive outside of the city you can find them everywhere. Okinawa isn’t just beaches, there are mountains and waterfalls and so much more to see! Add it to your must-do list in Japan. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/cherry-blossom-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/cherry-blossom-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Travel" /><summary type="html">It’s springtime! What does that mean? CHERRY BLOSSOM SEASON! Cherry Blossoms are the staple of living in Japan. It’s the highlight of being there. </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shop Goldies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/01/shop-goldies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shop Goldies" /><published>2019-05-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/01/shop-goldies</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/modeling/2019/05/01/shop-goldies.html">&lt;p&gt;Moving to California scared me. Leaving Japan scared me. I had created such a small group of creators who loved to photograph together. When I came to Cali I was afraid I wouldn’t find that. But I decided to reach out to this amazing Photographer Isaiah E. KajumbaI. I saw his work and was absolutely amazed by his style of photography.! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a few weeks of getting settled, he reached out to me and asked If I wanted to shoot with him and this local store in Downtown Ventura.. Goldies. OF COURSE, I DID! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hadn’t modeled in over a month! I was so excited and nervous but I did it. Take a look at some highlights. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need some advice on what to buy, hit me up! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/goldies/goldies-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Modeling" /><summary type="html">Moving to California scared me. Leaving Japan scared me. I had created such a small group of creators who loved to photograph together. When I came to Cali I was afraid I wouldn’t find that. But I decided to reach out to this amazing Photographer Isaiah E. KajumbaI. I saw his work and was absolutely amazed by his style of photography.! </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Maya Bay</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/30/maya-bay.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Maya Bay" /><published>2019-04-30T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-04-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/30/maya-bay</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/30/maya-bay.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ve seen The Beach right? That epic movie with Leonardo Dicaprio and the group of Travelers who live in Paradise? That movie is insane but that’s not the point. The point is, from that movie came the tourist destination in Thailand known as Maya Bay. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maya bay is one of the most beautiful destinations in Thailand. The beach is enclosed by three 100 meter cliffs on each side. (no you don’t have to swim to get there). The area has silky white sand, colorful corals, and exceptionally clear aqua water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least that’s what you read when you google “Maya Bay.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, the place is not as beautiful as described or as serene as the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/maya-bay-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all do to Tourism in Maya Bay. The tourist boom in the area has damaged the natural ecosystem of the area. Corals have been damaged by the insane amount of boats coming in and out of the area. The white sandy beaches have been littered by garbage tourists leave behind. And the clear aqua water is littered with long boats and speed carrying hoards of tourists. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On any given day, thousands of tourists come to Maya Bay. Therefore to get your famous “instagram worthy shot” you better be good at photoshopping. Or be an early riser who can get there before the crowds or after 5pm. But the problem is not many boats will go early or late so expect to be surrounded by loud music, loud people, no serenity or quiet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/maya-bay-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don’t get me wrong. The place is still worth a beautiful trip. When you go though, be delicate to the surrounding area and leave it as you found it. That means, TAKE YOUR TRASH. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to experience the full serenity and everything Maya Bay has to offer. I suggest doing Maya Bay Sleep Aboard. This once in a lifetime experience allows you to see the Bay without any footprints in the sand, no boats blocking your view, and hear the sound of the ocean, not over powered by the noise of people. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/thailand-2017-2018-2088.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/maya-bay-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through this tour, you get to actually sleep on a boat under the stars in the Bay. How cool is that?! At night you get to swim with the bioluminescent plankton. Something not many people can say they’ve done. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** At the time of this article, Maya Bay is closed indefinitely to correct and restore the natural ecosystem. ** &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Travel" /><summary type="html">You’ve seen The Beach right? That epic movie with Leonardo Dicaprio and the group of Travelers who live in Paradise? That movie is insane but that’s not the point. The point is, from that movie came the tourist destination in Thailand known as Maya Bay. </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Alternative Beach-Bali</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/05/alternative-beach-bali.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alternative Beach-Bali" /><published>2019-04-05T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-04-05T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/05/alternative-beach-bali</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel/2019/04/05/alternative-beach-bali.html">&lt;p&gt;Have you been to Bali yet? If not I highly suggest you go. The cafes and restaurants are amazing and you can’t go wrong. I am always on the hunt for a new cafe, restaurant, or chill out place when I travel. Luckily in Bali, I found Alternative Beach! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We first came here with the group from Institute of Code (more on that later) and I was blown away by all the suitable “instagram worthy” shots available. I swear, they designed this place in mind specifically for all you fabulous Instagrammers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/alternative-beach-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, the place is a hostel and a hotel all in one! Perfect for you budget travellers who love the hostel life, and crafted for the romantic lovers who want a private pool front villa. Creator thought of everything to appeal to the mass audiences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who doesn’t love a pool bar? I have no idea! Can’t think of a single person who’s had to complain and get out of the water to get their drink. Just swim on up order a cocktail, and sip it on one of the many floats they have available in the pool. Or chill out on the beachside walk in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/alternative-beach-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to work on your Bali Bod? (I think that should be new hashtag on instagram) They have you covered. Wanderlust Fitness Studio. Yes That is the name of the gym on the premises. Sadly I was enjoying the outdoors to much to go inside, but I saw it through a window. Looked Fabulous. Time to get fit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fact is short is sweet, when in Canggu head over to Alternative Beach for an evening of fun, drinks, laughter, and sweet content for your instagram that will last you weeks! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/alternative-beach-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Travel" /><summary type="html">Have you been to Bali yet? If not I highly suggest you go. The cafes and restaurants are amazing and you can’t go wrong. I am always on the hunt for a new cafe, restaurant, or chill out place when I travel. Luckily in Bali, I found Alternative Beach! </summary></entry></feed>